modresdes.com 2012-06-11

# Privacy Policy - Home Decorating Ideas – Interior Design Ideas on Modern Residential Design

What follows is the Privacy Statement for all Modresdes websites including all the websites run under the [http://www.modresdes.com](http://www.modresdes.com/).

Please read this statement regarding our blogs. If you have questions please ask us via our [contact form](http://www.modresdes.com/contact/).

**Email Addresses**  
You may choose to add your email address to our contact list via the forms on our websites. We agree that we will never share you email with any third party and that we will remove your email at your request. We don’t currently send advertising via email, but in the future our email may contain advertisements and we may send dedicated email messages from our advertisers without revealing your email addresses to them. If you have any problem removing your email address please contact us via our contact form.

**Comments/Message Boards**  
Most ModResDes.com websites contain comment sections (a.k.a. message boards). We do not actively monitor these comments and the information on them is for entertainment purposes only. If we are alerted to something we deem inappropriate in any way, we may delete it at our discretion. We use email validation on most of our message boards in order to reduce “comment spam.” These email addresses will not be shared with any third party.

**Cookies and Web Beacons**  
www.modresdes.com does use cookies to store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser.

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site such as Google (www.google.com/adsense) that use the DART cookie enables that place ads on our web site. For further information, consult the privacy policy of each those websites. You can choose to accept or decline cookies. To opt out of Google’s use of cookies, please visit the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html)

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on www.modresdes.com send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see.

www.modresdes.com has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. www.modresdes.com’s privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers’ respective websites.Traffic Reports

Our industry-standard traffic reporting records IP addresses, Internet service provider information, referrer strings, browser types and the date and time pages are loaded. We use this information in the aggregate only to provide traffic statistics to advertisers and to figure out which features and editorials are most popular.

**Business Transitions**  
If modresdes.com is acquired by or merges with another firm, the assets of our websites, including personal information, will likely be transferred to the new firm.

**Links**  
modresdes websites frequently link to other websites. We are not responsible for the content or business practices of these websites. When you leave our websites we encourage you to read the destination site’s privacy policy. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by modresdes.com

**Contact Information**  
If you have any questions regarding our privacy policy, please [contact us](http://www.modresdes.com/contact/).
